[
    {
        "age": 0,
        "id": "how-do-i-connect-to-itunes-store",
        "question": "iTunes Store",
        "snippet": "How do I connect to iTunes Store?",
        "badges": ["computer", "software", "apple"],
        "submitter": "Joe",
        "votes": 1,
        "answers": 2
    },
    {
        "age": 1,
        "id": "motorola-xoom",
        "question": "Largest state",
        "snippet": "Which state is the largest in the US?",
        "badges": ["geography", "US"],
        "submitter": "Mike",
        "votes": 3,
        "answers": 2
    },
    {
        "age": 2,
        "id": "motorola-atrix-4g",
        "question": "American football",
        "snippet": "How long is the halftime in a football game",
        "badges": ["sports", "football"],
        "submitter": "Bruce",
        "votes": 4,
        "answers": 1
    },
    {
        "age": 3,
        "id": "dell-streak-7",
        "question": "iPhone 5",
        "snippet": "How much does a contract-free iPhone 5 cost?",
        "badges": ["mobile", "price", "apple"],
        "submitter": "Alice",
        "votes": 6,
        "answers": 4
    },
    {
        "age": 4,
        "id": "samsung-gem",
        "question": "Football players",
        "snippet": "How many players are allowed on the field at once?",
        "badges": ["sports", "football"],
        "submitter": "George",
        "votes": 5,
        "answers": 2
    },
    {
        "age": 5,
        "id": "dell-venue",
        "question": "MP3 player",
        "snippet": "How do I transfer music from a computer to a MP3 player?",
        "badges": ["MP3", "music", "windows"],
        "submitter": "Zack",
        "votes": 8,
        "answers": 3
    },
    {
        "age": 6,
        "id": "nexus-s",
        "question": "Android development",
        "snippet": "Which IDE should I use in order to develop an Android application?",
        "badges": ["Android"],
        "submitter": "Lucia",
        "votes": 4,
        "answers": 9
    },
    {
        "age": 7,
        "id": "lg-axis",
        "question": "Mexican food",
        "snippet": "Which Mexican restraurant is the most highly rated in Atlanta?",
        "badges": ["food", "Mexican"],
        "submitter": "Bush",
        "votes": 3,
        "answers": 2
    },
    {
        "age": 8,
        "id": "samsung-galaxy-tab",
        "question": "Tennis star",
        "snippet": "Who is the world No.1 in ATP?",
        "badges": ["sports", "tennis"],
        "submitter": "Morgan",
        "votes": 8,
        "answers": 5
    },
    {
        "age": 9,
        "id": "samsung-showcase-a-galaxy-s-phone",
        "question": "Car insurance",
        "snippet": "How much does a new driver have to pay approximately for the car insurance each month?",
        "badges": ["car", "insurance", "deals"],
        "submitter": "Matt",
        "votes": 4,
        "answers": 5
    }
]
